BGM
Here we go... Upokami, this time with Risa Irie of JuiceJuice and
Risa Irie of JuiceJuice and Moe Kitahara of Ochanomimi.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at our two MCs.
I'm Irie, and the other day on May 15th, JuiceJuice released the AAA single “Love in Tokyo Murakamon”.
We released the AAA single “Aiiko” on May 15th, and we had a lot of release events.
We had a lot of release events and had a lot of chances to meet our fans.
I had a chance to meet with fans and received many warm words from them.
I really felt my heart warmed up.
After all, Iriemura-san's graduation...
Please enjoy your last day!
As it is the last single
Iriemura-san's last thing is increasing and increasing.
Iriemura-san's last release event and so on.
Iriemura-san's last release event, and his last local concert on his recent spring tour...
There have been various last events.
I have received a lot of “early early” from fans.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you so much!
When I saw people expressing their gratitude and crying, I realized that graduation is just around the corner, and I'd like to thank you all again.
I know I only have a few hours left, but I'd like to spend the rest of my time with you.
I would like to cherish the time I have with Mr. Iriemura for the rest of my life.
Yes, I, Kitahara...
I went to Okinawa the other day for the 47 prefectures tour.
I would like to talk about that time.
The day after the Okinawa concert
The day after the Okinawa concert, I went to Okinawa.
I went to Okinawa the day after the live concert in Okinawa
I went to Okinawa the day after the live concert in Okinawa!
I've never been snorkeling before.
It's really fun!
So I really want to try it someday!
So here we are, the two of us! And so, this time, we will be bringing you two such people.
Let's start off with a look at the making of BEYOND's HIGH TO DIAMOND music video.
Making of BEYOND's HIGH TO DIAMOND music video shooting
BEYOND'S HIGH TO DIAMOND music video making-of
BEYOND'S latest single
Please take a look at the making of the music video for BEYOND's HIGH TO DIAMOND!
Thank you for your hard work!
like this
I'm okay with this.
That's about all I ask.
Okay, here we go.
Yes, sound, please.
Okay, here we go!
Hey!
BOOM BOOM
BOOM BOOM BOOM
I think it came from outside.
Here we go.
Me.
I'm in.
I'm in! I'm going into the space we're putting it in!
I'm so happy. I never thought I'd be in a Japanese zoom music video.
I didn't think I'd get to be in the Tsuke in the Zoom Japan music video.
I'm in the Tsuke, but the location changes.
It's like...
It's like a door to anywhere.
Let's go inside.
Cut.
I'm coming out.
First one out.
I'll check the safety and come out.
Here we go.
Here we go
Okay, let's start Yo, start!
It's quite a lease.
I'm in.
Yes, it's Camon.
Yes, camon!
Yes, Kamon!
The setting of the music video is that the people of Beyond are actually making the whole country and the world a mirror world, and the phones are connected to the mirror world,
The phones are connected to the mirror world, and the drawers are used to warp to the mirror world to recharge the energy.
Okay, let's go.
Here we go.
Good morning.
This is my first visit to this studio.
Could it be...?
Oh, wait.
What, I like to eat.
Early, early.
Quick, quick.
That's not right.
Fast, fast.
Eight years different.
Good work.
The phone will ring,
Um, Mr. Nijin is going to answer the phone.
I'm in charge of the phone.
Wow.
I wonder.
I understand.
I'll be right there.
Laughter
Laughter.
laughter
laughter laughter
Laughter
I can do it, please.
Yes, we just filmed a scene where we, BEYOND, enter a dressing room for a TV show.
We did some lipsync and stuff like that.
It has the feel of a normal dressing room, but at the same time it has a cool feeling that matches the concept of this song.
But it also has a cool feeling that matches the concept of this song.
So you can see both sides of the scene.
Anyway, I think this song is going to show you the cool BEYOND.
I'll do my best to exceed your expectations!
I'll see you all soon!
Thank you very much for your hard work.
me
We had originally worked together on the shapes of the dances and the timing of the movements, but the silhouettes really showed the shapes perfectly, so we had to reorganize the choreography,
It was the first time we took silhouettes of the Beyons, but they looked so good that I wondered if it was really us.
We have a lot of dances, so please take a look.
Let's sing together
What kind of rags and tatters are you?
High to diamond
Even on an empty night
I want to make this star
I want to make it more mira mira mira
Mira Ball
Even if you burn up tonight
I'll make sure
High to diamond
My heart is open
Be more you
Don't be afraid to shine
Dream
Everyone, the next one will arrive.
Thank you very much
Let's shake it together
Let's shake it together Let's shake it together
No matter how battered and bruised you are
HIGH TO DIAMOND
Even on a new night
I want to make this star
I want to make this star more mira-mira
I want to make this star more mira mira mira
Uh Uh Uh
Even if I burn up tonight
I'll burn up tonight
HIGH TO DIAMOND
Not yet, Adalan
High to Diamond
Be more like you.
Be yourself
I want to sparkle
Let it be you
I want to bring it out, don't hold back, let it shine
Galaxy, sky, galaxy, drum load
Yes, we have finished shooting the music video for Hiteu Diamond.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was very difficult this time,
The choreography was difficult, as well as the lip scene solo shot at the end,
All mirrored inside the phone knox?
That was a first.
I had to shoot without the members being able to see where the camera was,
So we were shooting without being able to see the outside at all.
In that kind of space, I would find the camera and say, “Here I am,
It was very difficult to find the camera in such a space, to say, “Here,” and then to look at the camera and send a line of sight.
But it was fresh and fun.
There are a lot of dance shots in this music video,
I think you can enjoy the cool BEYOND to the fullest.
We also filmed the members going into the drawer and the members coming out,
So the music video has a bit of a storyline to it,
I hope you enjoy the music video and how it turned out.
Please take a look.
I saw the making of the music video for “Hi to DIAMOND,” and it was very cool, and I thought it was very nice that everyone was wearing silver costumes and accessories associated with diamonds. The first performance of this song was at Hinafest, wasn't it? I saw the making of the music video for “Hi to DIAMOND” and it was very cool, and I thought it was very nice that everyone was wearing silver costumes and accessories associated with diamonds. The first performance of this song was at Hinafest, wasn't it?
The first performance of this song was at the Hinafest, and JUSTUS and BEYONES were backstage next to each other, and they were practicing their “hammory” all the time. I went backstage to see them in person. They were so cool,
The singing was great, the dancing was great, and the song was filled with all the goodness that only the BEYONES can bring to the stage.
I thought the song had that kind of feel to it.
Yes, I, Kitahara, saw the scene where Mr. Yamazaki comes out of his desk. I thought it was cute when I saw the music video.
I wondered how it was done, so I was very happy to see the making of the video and to know that it was actually done,
Mr. Yamazaki must be happy, right?
I was also very happy to see the making of the film and to know that it was actually done.
I didn't think there would be a scene where you get out of your desk.
You mentioned it in the making of the film.
I never thought it would come true in the BEYOND music video.
It made me very happy too.
I thought it was a wonderful music video, filled with everyone's dreams.
I thought it was a wonderful music video.
That's all for BEYOND's Hi to Diamond
This is the making of the music video shooting.
Thank you very much.
No matter what kind of raggedy you are...
Hi to Diamond
Even on the right night
High to Diamond
More of those stars
Mira Mira
Beyond's High to Diamond
Now on sale
It's going to be good for you!
Next, here it is!
Yoshihiro Miyamoto, Polaris Compass, Making of the music video shooting
It was released on May 22nd!
The music video for the song “Polaris Compass” from Yoshibayashi Miyamoto's second album “Sequel” was shot on May 22nd.
Please take a look at the making of the music video for the song “Polaris Compass” from her second album “Sequel”!
Thank you for watching!
Now the music video shooting of Polaris Compass has started!
So, it was supposed to be unfortunate weather.
Unfortunately, the weather was supposed to be bad, but...
But it stopped raining somehow.
My cloudy woman power plus
plus my cloudy woman power of those who have come to this site.
She who is a woman of fine weather
or a woman who doesn't let it rain
The power of people from all walks of life
have gathered here now.
Will it rain or not?
Expect it!
Maybe it will!
Thank you for watching!
Though it wasn't magic that I could use
But I still shine a light
Following a sliver of the constellations
Even though I seem to lose my way
Glitter, glimmer, irreplaceable person
I already knew where I was headed
You already knew where you were headed
Not a big boat, but a handmade dream
I'm in love alone, and I don't need a place to be
Because I had the Tralis shining in my eyes
Lonely Night, dark and dreary with no shadows
I'm not afraid, but I'm not afraid
But now
I can believe
Why the stars and the songs are twinkling
Time is passing by
I'm so sad, so sad, so sad
But always look up
Thank you very much.
I think I've made enough.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
The music video shooting is over.
Please watch this music video as much as you can.
Bye bye.
You have also seen the making of the music video shooting of Polaris Compass.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I thought it was a really great song.
I also watched the music video,
Akari Miyamoto's face is so beautiful, and there was a close-up of her face,
I was watching it as if my heart was being purified, thinking that she is really beautiful.
I was watching her with a feeling of purification in my heart. The retro look of her first outfit, which looked like a casual dress, was also very nice,
And then Ms. Miyamoto in the purple dress was also very nice,
Her voice is so delicate and beautiful,
I thought that the purple dress really expressed how delicate and beautiful Miyamoto-san's voice was,
I thought it was a very enjoyable experience from the visuals as well.
That is all.
This is the making of the music video shooting for “Polaris Compass” by Yoshikazu Miyamoto.
Cheer up.
Okay, let's do this.
Yes, let's do it.
Do you have any questions?
I'm fine.
Okay, let's go to the melody.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I don't love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you...
I'm going to overflow tonight. Can you do it in your own voice?
I'll try!
Okay?
Okay.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
There's a part where it says “I love you” in the beginning.
Yes.
I wonder if I can make my voice thicker than it is now.
Oh! Yes, sir.
I understand.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I don't love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you...
You can continue or go to the same song.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I don't love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, Tokyo.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, Tokyo... I'll make a lady come true. It's gonna rain tomorrow.
Look, it's work. Why are you depressed?
Yeah, okay, okay. Why are you feeling down?
I'm feeling really stretched out, so...
I've got to go to work. I've got to go to work.
It's far away.
It's long.
I'm into the sloppy, lazy part, but...
I'm into the sloppy part, but yes.
I'd say it's very detailed, but it's a little long.
It's a little long.
It's work, right?
You got it.
I don't love you. I love you, too. Tokyo, tonight.
I'll make a lady come true. It's raining tomorrow.
You have to go to work. Why are you so depressed?
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
We can keep going, or we can do the same part of number two.
I'll go with that.
Okay.
Why are you depressed?
Because he's a stubborn, desperate foy... who can't be left alone... and he's a weakling.
Emotional story, time to get out of it, next corner.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes... when you get out of the emotional storyline, the rest is just a matter of...
I mean, it's a perfect frame-up here, too, but...
Yes, it is.
In terms of the groove.
Let's hear more.
I'll see if I can figure it out.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, okay.
Yes, okay.
Okay, let's go to the chorus.
Yes, sir.
That's it.
Yes, sir.Yes, ma'am.
I'm Manazami.
I'll throw a pie pan just in case.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Do you want to continue? Or do you want to go to the same place and go to number 2?
I'll continue.
Okay.
The first block is almost all backwards, isn't it?
New me, new Asami.
Is it tough here, too?
I'll be fine from here.
I can do it.
Then let's try it automatically from here.
Next block.
It's more like a gradient.
I can't connect here.
grad... night breeze gently brushing your hair back.
Yakaze... is it a little long?
The long night breeze...
Graduation... the night breeze gently brushing the back of your hair.
It's like “shaku” here with all my might.
Get out of the passenger seat of sleepless love
Let's go see a new morning with a new me
Graduation, the night wind that gently caresses the back of my hair
Yes, yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
That's all.
What? What is it, Mr. Taisei?
Yes, ma'am.
Goodbye.
Is there a last part?
You don't have to use it here. Fake it.
Fake it.
Oh.
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
oozing tokyo Tokyo that oozes
Ha-ha-ha!
This is no good.
The rest is oozing Tokyo
Tokyo
oozing east
smear east
Tokyo
oozing tokyo
yes
Yes
Budokan on Sunday
OK OK!
Yes!
Yes! Finish!
Thank you very much!
You have seen the recording video of Tokyo Blur!
I think it was a very typical Riai's recording video
I think it was very typical of Ria.
This song “Tokyo Blur” was written by Aoi Yamazaki, who has been a great help to me.
Mr. Aoi Yamazaki, who has always been a great help to us, wrote the lyrics.
Aoi Yamazaki, who has always been a great help to us, wrote the lyrics for this song.
The meaning of the word “blur” in “Tokyo Blur” is “unclear”.
the meaning of “Tokyo Blur” means “unclear”.
The song was written by Aoi Yamazaki, who has always been a great help to us, and it was written by Aoi Yamazaki.
the image of the main character will become clearer through the song.
It's a song that makes the main character's image become clearer and clearer.
It is full of Juice Juice's character.
It's a song that shows the strength of Juice Juice in all its aspects.
I think it's a song that shows the strength of Juice Juice in all its aspects.
In this song, the main member in charge is decided
The three songs of Tokyo Blur Naimono-Love Aiko
Tokyo Blur Naimono Love sang the main parts for each of the five members.
me and Riai, too.
I'm going to sing the Tokyo Blur one
I'm doing the main part and Riai is doing the
the Tokyo Blur team as the main singers.
Since the recording From the time of that recording.
I didn't know that we were going to split it 5-5.
When we received the recording and received the thank you for the song
I knew that we were going to divide them into 5-5 this time.
I didn't know that it would be like this at that time.
I didn't expect it to be like this at that time.
I didn't expect it to be like this at the time.
I didn't expect it to be like this at the time, but the fake arrangement at the end was very nice.
It took a lot of courage for me to be able to propose it.
I think it took a lot of courage
I think it's very brave of you.
And the way you are enjoying the sound is so like you.
I think it's wonderful.
I, Kitahara, love Matsunaga-san very much.
When I saw the music video of Tokyo Blur
When I saw the music video of Tokyo Blur, I really wanted to see the recording.
The way he enjoys the sound.
The way he enjoys the sound, the way he wants to try faking it.
the spirit to try something new.
It was something that I didn't have
It was something that wasn't popular with me yet.
So when I saw that
I felt like I had the power to have fun.
The power to have fun.
The way of life of the idols.
I could really see it.
I thought it was really cool.
I really like recording too, but
I really like to record, but I felt like I have the power to challenge myself
I really want to have the power to challenge something new on my own, and I think it's really great that you make me think that way.
That's all for JuiceJuice Tokyo Bra, Riai Matsunaga's vocal recording.
Angulum Bilital Ichigeki June 12 on SAIO
Thanks for watching.
This is Ilie Lisa and Momo Kitahara's Apkami.
It's time to say goodbye!
We've seen a lot of different videos this time.
I, Kitahara, was very impressed with the making of the music video for Beyonce's “High to Diamonds”.
I got to see it when it was first performed at the Hina Festival. I got to see them perform for the first time at the Hina Fest.
I saw their backs at the moment they started, and I watched them from right behind.
It was so cool.
I was so impressed by the way she shined her back.
When I watched the making of the music video for the song that left such an impression on me
I was reminded of the coolness of the sparkles and the silhouettes.
Also, the silhouette shooting was really cool.
And the silhouette shots were really cool too.
And I love the choreography.
I really love the choreography.
I'm really glad that I got to see the making of the film.
Yes, I, Rie, was very impressed with Ria Matsunaga's vocal recording.
I was really impressed by Rie Matsunaga's vocal recording.
You know how they faked it at the end?
The melody suddenly came to her in the bath.
He said he sang it as it was.
It's amazing how you keep coming up with new arrangements like that.
Whenever we perform together...
Ria Matsunaga arranges the sound well.
I'm always surprised that you can arrange the sound so well.
I don't know how to say it, but it makes me excited too.
I think that the many ways of arranging sounds is one of Ria's charms.
I want to enjoy the sound and absorb more and more of Ria's performance.
I want to absorb more and more of Ria's performance while enjoying her sound.
In this issue of APKAMI, we're going to take a closer look behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the Upfront Group.
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally see.
This time, our partners in crime are Risa Irie of JuiceJuice and Moe Kitahara of Ochanomama.
Good bye.
Next time on ATSUKAMI
The making of BEYOND GO! CITY GO! Music video shooting
and
BRILLIANCE OF MEMORIES: Recording by Kari Uemura!
Please look forward to it!
I wonder if I dropped this somewhere in the starry sky